[SNIFFS]
(Sheldon:)Smell that?
(Sheldon:)That's the smell of new comic books.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes.
(Howard:)They're on me today, boys.
(Raj:)You're paying?
Have you been selling your sperm again?
(Howard:)No, I'm celebrating.
(Howard:)As we speak, the space shuttle is docking
at the Internationale Space Station...
(Howard:)...where it will deploy the Wolowitz
Zero-Gravity Waste Disposal System.
(Raj:)Oh, get over yourself.
It's a high-tech toilet.
(Leonard:)Just think, thanks to your hard work...
(Leonard:)...an international crew of astronauts will
boldly go where no man has gone before.
- Is that supposed to be funny?
- I believe it is.
(Sheldon:)The Star Trek reference
and the play on words...
...involving the double meaning
of "to go"...
...suggest that Leonard is humorously
mocking your efforts in space plumbing.
(Howard:)Okay, make your little jokes.
But of the four of us...